[
    {
        "front": "しゅうみ",
        "back": "hobby",
        "chapter": "N4 C31"
    },
    {
        "front": "たいよう",
        "back": "sun",
        "chapter": "N4 C31"
    },
    {
        "front": "つき",
        "back": "moon",
        "chapter": "N4 C31"
    },
    {
        "front": "あがる",
        "back": "to rise",
        "chapter": "N4 C31"
    },
    {
        "front": "さがる",
        "back": "to go down",
        "chapter": "N4 C31"
    },
    {
        "front": "ふかい",
        "back": "deep",
        "chapter": "N4 C31"
    },
    {
        "front": "あさい",
        "back": "shallow",
        "chapter": "N4 C31"
    },
    {
        "front": "つる",
        "back": "to fish",
        "chapter": "N4 C31"
    },
    {
        "front": "つり",
        "back": "fishing",
        "chapter": "N4 C31"
    },
    {
        "front": "たいてい",
        "back": "most of",
        "chapter": "N4 C31"
    },
    {
        "front": "たまに",
        "back": "every now and then",
        "chapter": "N4 C31"
    },
    {
        "front": "やく",
        "back": "to roast",
        "chapter": "N4 C31"
    },
    {
        "front": "つれていく",
        "back": "to take ~ to",
        "chapter": "N4 C31"
    },
    {
        "front": "むかし",
        "back": "in the past",
        "chapter": "N4 C31"
    },
    {
        "front": "おもいだす",
        "back": "to recall",
        "chapter": "N4 C31"
    },
    {
        "front": "かない",
        "back": "wife",
        "chapter": "N4 C31"
    },
    {
        "front": "てつだう",
        "back": "to help",
        "chapter": "N4 C31"
    }
]